http://www.industrios.com/legal/privacy-policy

905 829 2525
Contact
What do you need?
PlantCare
PlantUP!
Menu
What do you need?
PlantCare
PlantUP!
INDUSTRIOS Software Privacy Policy
You get it. We get it.
We live, breathe, walk, speak, eat and sleep discrete manufacturing operations.
Let's talk shop
OPEN NAVIGATION
Overview
Our site visitors’ privacy and trust are important to us. We provide this notice in order to make sure that your expectations and our practices are aligned, and that you are aware of your choices with regard to our use and disclosure of the information you provide to our site.
This Privacy Policy describes the policies of INDUSTRIOS Software ("we"), regarding the collection, use, disclosure and protection of the following types of information:
Information obtained when you (“you”or “User”) visit the web site
Information obtained through e-mail communications with you related to the Site.
This privacy policy does not apply to information we collect by other means (including offline) or from other sources. Your use of our Site constitutes your acceptance of this Privacy Policy and your consent to any action we take with respect to your information in compliance with this Privacy Policy.
We may change the terms of this Privacy Policy, so Users are encouraged to review this page from time to time. Your continued use of our Site following the posting of changes to the Privacy Policy means that you accept the changes.
Information We Collect and How We Collect It
We require you to provide certain information about yourself if you register with our Site or request products and services. We also collect information when you participate in contests, surveys, and when you respond to requests for feedback.
The information we collect may include information from which you may be personally identified ("Personally Identifiable Information"), such as name, postal address, telephone number, fax number and e-mail address, and certain business information such as employer name, occupation, job function, job title and buying information (e.g., preferences or history). Our Site only collects Personally Identifiable Information with your knowledge.
When you visit our Site, we may collect the IP address of your computer. We also use automatic data collection technology to record other information that identifies your computer and tracks your behavior on our Site. Methods used to collect this information may include "cookies" and "clear GIFs" (also known as "pixel tags" or "beacons"). A cookie is a small amount of data that is sent to your browser from a server and stored on your computer’s hard drive. Most browsers allow Users to block the receipt of cookies, but doing so may compromise your ability to use certain features of our Site.  We do not collect Personally Identifiable Information in this way, but if you provide us with Personally Identifiable Information, we may associate that information with the information that is collected automatically.
How We Use Your Information
We use Personally Identifiable Information collected on our Site for the following purposes:
To provide you with our Site and other products and services.
To respond to your inquiries and contact you about changes regarding our Site.
For any other purpose disclosed at the time the information is collected or to which you consent.
As otherwise specifically described in this Privacy Policy.
We also may use your information to better understand our Users and to improve our Site. For example, we may use this information to determine what portions of our Site are most popular and the demographics of our Users generally. Cookies and other User information also enable us to customize your experience on the Site. We may use IP addresses to help diagnose problems with our servers or to administer our Site. We may also use IP addresses to help identify a User during a particular session and to gather data regarding use of our Site.
We may use the information you provide us to send you e-mail, fax and other communications on behalf of INDUSTRIOS Software and our affiliates. These communications may include e-mail newsletters, as well as offers for other INDUSTRIOS Software services. All email newsletters will provide you with an opportunity to opt out of receiving future issues of the newsletter. All promotional offers will include an opportunity to opt out of receiving future promotions from the brand whose product/service is being promoted.
We also may use your information to send you e-mail and other communications on behalf of third parties.  Each of these communications will include instructions for opting out of receiving future third party offers from us. You may also opt out of receiving third party offers from our Site at any time by sending an e-mail to marketing@industrios.com with the subject line "opt out – third party."
Our Disclosure of Your Information
We may disclose aggregated, anonymous statistics about many Users, and individual information that is not Personally Identifiable Information without restriction as long as no individual is identifiable by the information disclosed, and otherwise will not disclose your Personally Identifiable Information except as follows:
When we believe such disclosure is required by law, regulation or securities exchange requirement or for the protection of persons or property.
When disclosure is necessary to accomplish the purpose for which you provide it.
Security
We use reasonable safeguards to protect Personally Identifiable Information we collect on our Site from unauthorized access, use, modification or disclosure. However, due to the design of the Internet and other factors outside of our control, we cannot guarantee that communications between you and our servers will be free from unauthorized access by third parties.
Right to Access and Change Information
You may view and update information that you previously submitted to our Site by sending an e-mail to marketing@industrios.com. However, a request to change information may not be accommodated if the request would conflict with legal requirements or result in incorrect information. Requests to view or change personal information may take a few days to process.
Links
Our Site contains content, services, advertising and other materials that link to Web sites operated by third parties. We have no control over those other sites, and this Privacy Policy does not apply to them. We encourage you to refer to the privacy policies, if any, of those sites.
Our Site is operated by:
